SHANNON HINDERBERGER

DIGITAL MARKETING PROFESSIONAL

shanlee@gmail.com

541-390-1068

SOCIAL



@eelnahs



@shanlee

PROFILE

I'm a marketing professional with over 15 years of experience. I research, plan, manage and execute online and offline marketing initiatives including content strategy, search engine optimization, paid search engine marketing, email marketing, social media, public relations, online reputation management and brand development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Digital Strategist

The Growler Guys 2016 - Present Bend, Oregon

Marketing Manager

Riverhouse Hotel & Convention Ctr. 2012 - 2016 Bend, Oregon

Independent Contractor

Digital Marketing Strategist 2010-present

Marketing Projects Coordinator

Bend Memorial Clinic 2007-2012 Bend, Oregon

Director of Marketing & Campaign

United Way of Deschutes County 2004-2007 Bend, Oregon

Director of Development & PR

Nebraska Food Bank 2002-2004 Omaha, Nebraska

Content Specialist

Cox Interactive Media 1998-2002 Omaha, Nebraska

News Producer

Cox Communications 1997-1998 Omaha, Nebraska

News Intern/Production Assistant

KMTV 1996-1997 Omaha, Nebraska

EXPERTISE& SKILLS

- Brand Development
- Project Development
- Strategic Planning
- Public Relations
- Content Strategy & Development
- · Email Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Targeted Digital Marketing
- · Social Media Marketing
- Online Reputation Management
- Website Project Management
- Sales Support
- Direct Mail
- Graphic Design & Production
- Google Analytics & Webmaster Tools
- Visual Presentations

EDUCATION

1993-1997

Bachelor of Arts, Broadcast Communications University of Nebraska - Omaha

AWARDS

Accomplished 40 under 40 Award Bend, Oregon

AFFILIATIONS

SWIVEL Digital Marketing Conf. Content Marketing Chair 2011- Present

Central Oregon Beer Angels Member 2013-present

References available upon request